yoshop.com 2017-01-29

# Privacy Policy | Yoshop

### Privacy Policy

Yoshop respect the privacy of our visitors/customers, which is extremely important to us. We take your online safety seriously. To better serve you and to make you understand how your information is used on our APP, we have explained our privacy policy below. 

### 1.The information we collect

We believe it’s important for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our APP. The information includes your Email, Name, Company Name, Street Address, Post Code, City, Country, Telephone Number, Password and so on. We collect this information in several different ways; to begin with, we use cookies that are needed to compile and aggregate non-personally identifiable information about the visitors to our APP. Personally identifiable information consists of information that is unique to you, such as credit card number and bank account numbers. The information is unique to you. 

### 2.The use of information

Help us make this APP easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. Helps you quickly locate information, products, and services. Helps us create content on this APP that is most relevant to you. Alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer. 

### Registration and Ordering:

During registration, you will be prompted to provide us your name, shipping and billing address, phone number, email address and credit card number. In addition, we may also ask you for your country so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations, and we might also ask for your gender. These types of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our APP, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we may use the personal information you provide us with to contact you. 

### Email Addresses:

You register for placing an order and receiving free promotional notices; we notify you when we receive a new brand, or new product style; to get there great offers, you simply sign up for our email newsletter. Your participation in a contest is completely voluntary, and you may choose whether to participate and disclose information to us. 

### 3.Privacy Security

We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to other companies as part of our regular course of business. We use the latest in encryption technology, and all employees that we do hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them from disclosing any information to which the employee has access, to other individuals or entities. 

### What kind of email do you send to the customer?

We send email content to our customers that may include following: Transaction mail, Shipping notification, Weekly deal, Promotion, Activity. 

### How do I unsubscribe?

You can unsubscribe by using the link from any email newsletter or your personal subscribe setting after logged in. 

    Email: support@yoshop.com
    Phone:（+1）866 990 1222 --- US Customers only
                 (+001)866 990 1222 --- International Customers
